<resources>
    <string name="app_name">iStock</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="date">datePicker</string>
    <string name="agreement_text"><![CDATA[<font color=\'#EA0606\'>User Agreement </font> is a legally binding contract between you and the Application, governing your use of the application. By using the Application, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>1. Acceptance of Terms</font> By downloading, installing, or using the Application, you agree to comply with and be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use the Application. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>2. License and Usage</font> We grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to use the Application for personal, non-commercial purposes only. You may not modify, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, or attempt to derive the source code of the Application. Use the Application in a manner that violates any applicable laws or regulations. Share your account information or credentials with others. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>3. Privacy</font> your use of the Application is also governed by our Privacy Policy. By using the Application, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in our Privacy Policy. <br><br>
<font color=\'#EA0606\'>4. Content</font> you are solely responsible for any content you submit through the Application. You agree not to submit content that is unlawful, defamatory, obscene, or infringing on any third-party rights. We may, at our sole discretion, remove or block content that violates this Agreement. <br><br><font color=\'#EA0606\'>5. Intellectual Property</font> The Application, including its design, text, graphics, logos, and other content, is protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws. You may not reproduce, distribute, or create derivative works from the Application without our prior written consent. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>6. Termination</font> We reserve the right to terminate or suspend your access to the Application at our sole discretion, without notice, for any reason, including if we believe you have violated this Agreement. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>7. Disclaimer</font> THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. <br><br>
<font color=\'#EA0606\'>8. Limitation of Liability</font> TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, COMPANY SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, OR ANY LOSS OF PROFITS OR REVENUES, WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>9. Changes to Agreement</font> We may update this Agreement from time to time, and any changes will be effective upon posting the revised Agreement on the Application. You are encouraged to review this Agreement periodically to ensure that you understand and agree with the latest version. <br><br> <font color=\'#EA0606\'>10. Contact Information</font> If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Agreement, please contact us at [Your Contact Information].<br><br>By using the Application, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the Application.]]></string>
    <string name="client_id">1069207649541-4uq1fv873gkh90i54optv6fth29c470k.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="nav_bar">Search here…</string>
    <string name="back"><![CDATA[<-]]></string>
    <string name="forward"><![CDATA[->]]></string>
    <string name="brand">BRAND</string>

    <string-array name="labels_array">
        <item>Quantity In</item>
        <item>Quantity Out</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>